percent up to 75 percent for
precipitation so a little uptick
there and you can see two weeks
ago
Rockies and of the last seven
days much more significant and
coverage statewide, which is
what we were expecting. So
We got skipped for the most
part. I got 0.47 inches of rain
with that storm a couple nights
a look at severe weather the
climatology through the late
spring and into the summer you
can
there but the last week of July
it really decreases things are
get a lot
quieter as severe weather goes
excessive moisture it‘s really
precipitation and that‘s not
severe
that‘s not severe weather unless
you have floods but that‘s a
different
warning category so we do have a
little chance of mainly wind
Continued chance of convection
for Saturday. It‘s really in the
mountains and just maybe a storm
or two
front draped along it is cooler
out there low 80s so kind of
nice on Thursday
We have the potential for heavy
flooding rains with
thunderstorms and the severe is
out here in Kansas.
the coverage precipitation on
Friday. And it‘s Western
Colorado for Saturday. Really, I
don‘t
25 but we‘ll see. We are topped
out with our maximum temperature
day and night 60 and 90.
For August 1st 2008 record low
42. That‘s the record low for
all of
occurred occurred on the 31st
and 1873 and the next day 1995
I‘ll go back
And that brings in cloudiness
Monday through Friday. So
definitely decreasing sunlight
and